

KISHAN VAGHELA

Mobile App Developer

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Android
Java
React Native
JavaScript
Git / SVN
Project management
Layout design

PERSONAL SKILLS

Reliable and professional Team player Fast learner Motivated

CONTACT

Phone: +91 9913541399

Email: kishan@creolestudios.com Skype: kishan.creolestudios LinkedIn: lnked.in/kishanvaghela GitHub: github.com/Kishanjvaghela

ABOUT

A forward thinking developer having three years of experience building, integrating, testing and supporting Android applications for mobile and tablet devices.

I also have experience working in React-Native mobile app developments. I like writing efficient, maintainable and reusable code. Proficient in design, data structures, problem-solving, and debugging

WORK EXPERIENCE

REACT-NATIVE / ANDROID APP DEVELOPER

Creole Studios, Ahmedabad | Jul 2015 - PRESENT

- Developed react native and android applications and Design app architecture
- Developed libraries in gradle and modules in npm
- Team handling and training freshers for android app development.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Avinashi Group of Companies, Surat | Jun 2014 - Jul 2015

- Developed android apps and deployed the app on the Android Play Store
- Supported the app for different releases of Android OS and added new features in deployed app.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING. COMPUTER SCIENCE

Gujarat Technological University | 2010 - 2014 CGPA 7.17

CERTIFICATIONS

REACT NATIVE AND REDUX COURSE

Udemy | Feb 2017

PYTHON & LINUX WORKSHOP

IIT Bombay, APRIL 2013